Register of the Poland. Ambasada (France) Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- TELEGRAMS, 1919-1940
  - General.
    - Bucharest
      - General
        - 1939
          - Outgoing (Box 13)
            - December (Folder 13: 4)
        - 1940
          - Incoming
            - January (Folder 13: 5)
            - February (Folder 13: 6)
            - March (Folder 13: 7)
          - Outgoing
            - February (Folder 13: 8)
            - March (Folder 13: 9)
            - April (Folder 13: 10)
            - May-June (Folder 13: 11)
      - Letters, 1940
        - Incoming, September (Folder 13: 12)
        - Outgoing
          - January-March (Folder 13: 13)
          - April-May (Folder 13: 14)
          - August-September (Folder 13: 15)
    - Budapest
      - 1939
        - Incoming
          - September (Folder 13: 16)
          - October (Folder 13: 17)
          - November (Folder 13: 18)
          - December (Folder 13: 19)
        - Outgoing
          - September (Folder 13: 20)
          - October (Folder 13: 21)
          - November (Folder 13: 22)
          - December (Folder 13: 23)
      - 1940 January-May
        - Incoming (Folder 13: 24)
        - Outgoing (Folder 13: 25)
    - Cairo
      - 1939
        - Incoming, September-November (Folder 13: 26)
        - Outgoing, October-November (Folder 13: 27)
      - 1940 - Incoming (Folder 13: 28)
    - Catholic Church, 1939 - Incoming (Folder 13: 29)
    - Copenhagen, 1939 September-November
      - Incoming (Folder 13: 30)
      - Outgoing (Folder 13: 31)
    - Geneva
      - General
        - 1932 - Incoming (Folder 13: 32)
        - 1937
          - Incoming (Folder 13: 33)
          - Outgoing (Folder 13: 34)
        - 1938
          - Incoming (Folder 13: 35)
          - Outgoing (Folder 13: 36)
      - Letters
        - 1937
          - Incoming (Folder 13: 37)
          - Outgoing (Folder 13: 38)
        - 1938
          - Incoming (Folder 13: 39)
          - Outgoing (Folder 13: 40)
      - Reports, 1932 - Incoming (Folder 13: 41)
    - Hague, The (Box 14)
      - 1939
        - Incoming, September-November (Folder 14: 1)
        - Outgoing, October-December (Folder 14: 2)
      - 1940
        - Incoming, April (Folder 14: 3)
        - Outgoing, April-May (Folder 14: 4)
    - Helsinki
      - 1937 - Outgoing (Folder 14: 5)
      - 1939 - Incoming, September-November (Folder 14: 6)
      - 1940
        - Incoming, February-April (Folder 14: 7)
        - Outgoing
          - February (Folder 14: 8)
          - March (Folder 14: 9)
    - Jerusalem, 1939 September-November
      - Incoming (Folder 14: 10)
      - Outgoing (Folder 14: 11)
    - Kaunas, 1939
      - Incoming, September-October (Folder 14: 12)
      - Outgoing, October (Folder 14: 13)
    - Lisbon
      - 1937
        - Incoming (Folder 14: 14)
        - Outgoing (Folder 14: 15)
      - 1938 - Incoming, September-November (Folder 14: 16)
      - 1939 - Outgoing, November-December (Folder 14: 17)
      - 1940
        - Incoming, March-September (Folder 14: 18)
        - Outgoing, January-September (Folder 14: 19)
    - London
      - General
        - 1937
          - Incoming (Folder 14: 20)
          - Outgoing (Folder 14: 21)
        - 1938
          - Incoming (Folder 14: 22)
          - Outgoing (Folder 14: 23)
        - 1939
          - Incoming
            - March-July (Folder 14: 24)
            - August (Folder 14: 25)
            - September (Folder 14: 26)
            - October (Folder 14: 27)
            - November (Folder 14: 28)
            - December (Folder 14: 29)
          - Outgoing
            - September (Folder 14: 30)
            - October (Folder 14: 31)
            - November (Folder 14: 32)
            - December (Folder 14: 33)
        - 1940
          - Incoming, February-July (Folder 14: 34)
          - Outgoing, January-June (Folder 14: 35)
      - Letters
        - 1937
          - Incoming (Folder 14: 36)
          - Outgoing (Folder 14: 37)
        - 1938
          - Incoming (Folder 14: 38)
          - Outgoing (Folder 14: 39)
      - Reports, 1932 - Incoming (Folder 14: 40)
    - Madrid
      - 1937
        - Incoming (Folder 15: 1)
        - Outgoing (Folder 15: 2)
      - 1938
        - Incoming (Folder 15: 3)
        - Outgoing (Folder 15: 4)
      - 1939 - Incoming, February-November (Folder 15: 5)
      - 1940
        - Incoming, July-September (Folder 15: 6)
        - Outgoing, April-September (Folder 15: 7)
    - Moscow
      - 1937
        - Incoming (Folder 15: 8)
        - Outgoing (Folder 15: 9)
      - 1939 - Incoming (Folder 15: 10)
    - Oslo, 1937
      - Incoming (Folder 15: 11)
      - Outgoing (Folder 15: 12)
    - Prague - Incoming, 1938 (Folder 15: 13)
    - Riga
      - 1937 - Outgoing (Folder 15: 14)
      - 1939 - Incoming (Folder 15: 15)
    - Rome
      - General
        - 1937
          - Incoming (Folder 15: 16)
          - Outgoing (Folder 15: 17)
        - 1938
          - Incoming (Folder 15: 18)
          - Outgoing (Folder 15: 19)
        - 1939
          - Incoming, January-October (Folder 15: 20)
          - Outgoing, September-October (Folder 15: 21)
      - Letters
        - 1937
          - Incoming (Folder 15: 22)
          - Outgoing (Folder 15: 23)
        - 1938
          - Incoming (Folder 15: 24)
          - Outgoing (Folder 15: 25)
    - Sofia, 1939 - Incoming, August-September (Folder 15: 26)
    - Stockholm
      - 1937 - Incoming (Folder 15: 27)
      - 1938
        - Incoming (Folder 15: 28)
        - Outgoing (Folder 15: 29)
      - 1939 - Incoming, September (Folder 15: 30)
    - Tallin, 1937
      - Incoming (Folder 15: 31)
      - Outgoing (Folder 15: 32)
    - Teheran, 1937
      - Incoming (Folder 15: 33)
      - Outgoing (Folder 15: 34)
    - Vienna, 1938
      - General
        - Incoming (Folder 15: 35)
        - Outgoing (Folder 15: 36)
      - Letters, Incoming (Folder 15: 37)
    - Warsaw
      - Instructions, Incoming
        - 1934 (Folder 15: 38)
        - 1935 (Folder 15: 39)
        - 1936 (Folder 15: 40)
        - 1937 (Folder 15: 41)
      - Letters
        - 1937
          - Incoming (Folder 15: 42)
          - Outgoing (Folder 15: 43)
        - 1938
          - Incoming (Folder 15: 44)
          - Outgoing (Folder 15: 45)
    - Washington
      - 1937
        - Incoming (Folder 15: 46)
        - Outgoing (Folder 15: 47)
      - 1939 September
        - Incoming (Folder 15: 48)
        - Outgoing (Folder 15: 49)
      - 1940 - Outgoing, August-September (Folder 15: 50)
  - Foreign Ministry (Box 16)
    - Incoming
      - 1924 December - 1925 September (Folder 16: 1)
      - 1926 August - 1927 July (Folder 16: 2)
      - 1927 July - 1928 May (Folder 16: 3)
      - 1928 May - 1929 March (Folder 16: 4)
      - 1929 March - 1931 September (Box-folder 17: 1)
      - 1931 September - 1932 April (Folder 17: 2)
      - 1933 April - 1935 December (Folder 17: 3)
      - 1936 January - 1937 February (Box-folder 18: 1)
      - 1937
        - January-June (Folder 18: 2)
        - July-December (Folder 18: 3)
      - 1938
        - January-March (Folder 18: 4)
        - April-June (Folder 18: 5)
        - July-September (Folder 18: 6)
        - October-December (Folder 18: 7)
      - 1939
        - January-March (Folder 18: 8)
        - April-June (Folder 18: 9)
        - July (Folder 18: 10)
        - August (Folder 18: 11)
        - September (Folder 18: 12)
        - October (Folder 18: 13)
      - 1940 February-March(2 leaves) (Folder 18: 14)
    - Outgoing (Box 19)
      - 1924 May - 1925 March (Folder 19: 1)
      - 1925 March - 1926 January (Folder 19: 2)
      - 1926 January - 1927 January (Folder 19: 3)
      - 1927 January - 1927 October (Box-folder 20: 1)
      - 1927 October - 1928 December (Folder 20: 2)
      - 1928 December - 1929 December (Folder 20: 3)
      - 1929 December - 1931 June (Folder 20: 4)
      - 1931 June - 1932 August (Box-folder 21: 1)
      - 1932 August - 1934 June (Folder 21: 2)
      - 1934 June - 1937 February (Box-folder 22: 1)
      - 1937
        - January-March (Folder 22: 2)
        - April-June (Folder 22: 3)
        - July-September (Folder 22: 4)
        - October-December (Folder 22: 5)
      - 1938
        - January-March (Folder 22: 6)
        - April-June (Folder 22: 7)
        - July-September (Folder 22: 8)
        - October-December (Folder 22: 9)
      - 1939 (Box 23)
        - January-February (Folder 23: 1)
        - March-April (Folder 23: 2)
        - May-June (Folder 23: 3)
        - July-August (Folder 23: 4)
        - September
          - 1-10 (Folder 23: 5)
          - 11-18 (Folder 23: 6)
  - Polish diplomatic posts - Incoming.
    Logbooks
    - 1924 January - 1926 March (Folder 23: 7)
    - 1926 April - 1931 May (Folder 23: 8)
- PRINTED MATTER, 1941-1943
  - Biuletyn informacyjny dla Spraw Zydostwa Plskiego, no. 9, 1941 (Folder 23: 9)
  - Dziennik Ustaw, nos. 2-9, 1941 (Folder 23: 10)
  - Sprawy Slaska Cieszynskiego: Biuletyn, no. 6, 1943 (Folder 23: 11)
  - Szyfr Nr. 50. Szyfrant
    - General (Folder 23: 12)
    - Circulars, 1942 (Folder 23: 13)